Fear has a new face.
The Forgotten Ones is a horror, action film directed by Jörg Ihle.
When a devastating boat crash shipwrecks a group of friends in the jungles of an uncharted island,
they are savagely picked off one-by-one by a cannibalistic enemy that evolution forgot.
Liz, played by Jewel Staite.
Peter, played by Justin Baldoni.
Jake, played by Kellan Lutz.
Ira, played by Marc Bacher.
Lauren, played by Nikki Griffin.
Myra, played by Helena Barrett.
The Forgotten (also known as Don't Look in the Basement and Death Ward
#13) is a 1973 independent horror film directed by S.
Brownrigg, written by Tim Pope and starring Bill McGhee, former Playboy model Rosie Holotik, and
Annabelle Weenick (credited as Anne MacAdams) about homicidal patients at an insane asylum.
The film explores themes of island, shipwreck, cannibal, uncharted.
The tone is dark.